busy day how internal are not using good
technique this is really always talk
about this I don't know why someone that
its ok to use back acne holyfield is
actually talk about what the hell is not
give you $100 worth of information on
them he seemed like a good that will
allow you actually is to get Palace
think our staff are used to determine no
matter what the weather about them using
good or bad technique fully understand
the purpose of the exercise now stop
right here it's a lot of people don't
pay attention to this lecture by the
damper on the first place
let's hope you have a coach that you
work and you have a very clear
understanding of the exact purpose of
the exercise exact position of the body
while this group resist while I'm
feeling West answers here with my stance
quick example let's say vs The Lorax so
far back so often using things like
libby is a very versatile or so
your season very former cop your toes so
you can see very versatile because the
Lord is directly on your back that's
very very different holiday style or
roll over the summer to keep the ball
rolling off your back you mean for
alright so what happens is your knees
actually stayed behind in school almost
like this hired good morning
different if you want to know whether
he's a good technique understand are we
trying to do more for me he trying to
keep this in turn is so I should be
sitting back is a little more if not
made him back to back because I create
course here and we hear back this all
changes have been a family suffer
through the desired rating now our
default should be four regional right
through each do what we want every young
was designed to do what we have to
realize that all four major bullshit and
we'll talk about these
but we understand the point of this
exercise program selection desiring more
naughty thriller 34 step system I'm not
gonna do now we all used to determine
where some of the body position their
number two on a flexible joints
ligaments tendons and muscles in the
position we wanted to be in number three
symmetrical front back or left and right
sides one day out there that was over
here
other things like that for the state
Division accessible lawful good example
is your vehicle right hand motion
position but you need to make it look
like a word of the supposed to be in
good possibility into the right to
motion and probably sessions and
generally means finding draw everything
else i symmetrical back side the side so
if I match in this room is loaded right
for you to tell them
3535 things like that can I delete this
purpose to school and life in general
wanna make sure any exercise you use it
to help you determine whether or not
he's a good thing or bad thing
comfortable website indiegogo.com
there right now want to see next to
check for expanded to 25 minutes she
listens well stop in or call this number